{
    "id": "d33cbbec2e744f9fb7115f5ee9d4a1fc",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There was …………………………. hope.",
            "description": "Use little with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0b624bf764e64c02827798f6237a912a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know …………………………. guy who works in Australia?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "any",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b2a1ce21b38e4690a0d9a96ff961a85b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met ………………………. pretty girls in the store.",
            "description": "Much is used with uncountable nouns. Use some in affirmative sentences. ",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb31d10318994099948b41a8b0b728a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited …………………………… my friends.",
            "description": "Either all or all of can be used before a noun with a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "all of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "71513edd3f6c4406a263b107cd1c9478"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited …………………………… friend I have.",
            "description": "Use all and some with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "some"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d380b3188f2d49a4a9930207b482e45f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can’t waste …………………….. more time on this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "116bbea9a77b4ab1a32dcb4291740594"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is too ……………………….. salt in the soup.",
            "description": "Use much with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "66197b81a3264702839d71770ad1d5b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. birds can sing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "All",
                "Any"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5199b9522dd44cba582405759f11c76"
        },
        {
            "question": "Should I add ………………………….. more salt to the soup?",
            "description": "A little indicates a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e8eadc30540747bead983e1e30cffd59"
        },
        {
            "question": "Only ……………………… members voted in favor of the proposal.",
            "description": "A few indicates a small number. A little indicates a small quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "69d46718003547ddad9a694958f35a24"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. money that I had was spent on drinks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "da5f1b80c1954ad4bf15011af4d5e06e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ………………………. town was talking about the explosion.",
            "description": "All goes before the article whole goes after the article. ",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "whole",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "33a3e2539e2b4a309c845f85ac7a4bdf"
        }
    ]
}